Q1: Why might we consider using Git?

Answer: Git is useful for tracking changes to files over time, working other people, and changing back to previous versions of files.

Q2: What field could data science be applied to? Give an Example.

Answer: Data science could be applied to healthcare. It can be used to analyze patient data to discover what patients may be susceptible to certain sicknesses and other issues.

Q3: What is the difference between Merging and Rebasing?

Answer: Merging "merges" two branches through creating a new merge commit, which preserves the history of the file. Rebasing moves a branch's commits on top of another branch to create a linear history, rewriting past commits.